Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Be careful, Osman.
I need you.
Where are you going?
Where are you going? Come at me!
You aren't alone, Osman Bey!
Who is that woman?
Attack! Attack!
Kill them!
We are here, my bey!
The lord! Osman Bey, catch the lord!
Boran, Gencebay; help Bamsı Bey!
-Are you all right, my bey?
-Kids...
I'm all right, kids.
Charge! It's the day of honor!
My holy Allah, protect us.
Lower your weapons!
-Drop your weapons, Gündüz Bey!
-Hold!
I told you to lower them!
Hold!
Gündüz Bey.
Gündüz Bey!
Lower it.
Lower!
Bring me a cart! Dündar Bey and
the women will come with me!
If someone follows us, I'll kill
them all!
Bring a cart!
Charge! Charge!
Kill them!
Who are you, woman?
Don't pollute your hands with the
blood of the heathen.
The blood of the heathen can't
pollute anything of ours.
Honorable Ertuğrul Ghazi's son,
Osman Bey.
My bey!
-Are you all right, my bey?
-I'm all right.
-How is Bamsı Bey?
-Gencebay took him, my bey.
Will we go after Nikola?
Even if he was lying,
we'll take our measures.
We'll be at the tribe at once.
Come on!
I will come with you.
You haven't told me who you are, woman.
Kızılbey's son Umur Bey's
daughter Malhun Hatun.
We came for jihad.
-Umur Bey's daughter, huh?
-He sent me as an envoy.
We were destined to meet like this.
-Come on.
-My bey, Savcı Bey might be ambushed.
This isn't the first time they are
ambushed. They can take care of it.
Come on!
You won't run away, Savcı Bey.
I will finish you here.
Hang on, valiants.
Hang on!
Our Allah will help us.
We need to get out of here and go
to a cave. They can't stop us at night.
Son!
Come on.
-Father!
-Daughter...
-Is this how we meet, father?
-Allah is the one who decides.
Be patient.
Targun!
-Let her go!
-No one can stop me, Selcan Hatun.
-I told you to let her go!
-Stop!
Aunt, aunt, stop.
What are you saying, Gündüz?
Don't you see that they are taking
the women and Dündar?
They seized Osman's escrows!
-I will stop this!
-Aunt! Aunt!
They took our loved ones captive,
don't you see?
-Do you want them to die? Don't.
-They can't do this!
-I won't let them. Move!
-Selcan Hatun!
My sheik.
My sheik, don't you see?
They have Osman's escrows.
My sheik, they took Osman's wife
as a captive.
She is my precious daughter, Selcan Hatun.
Let us leave revenge to Osman Bey.
We should be patient.
Father...
Göktuğ... Göktuğ!
May you burn in hell, Göktuğ!
May you lose your hands!
May you never live a happy day, Göktuğ!
Bayhoca!
I hope you've fulfilled your longing with
your son, Savcı.
This is the last time you see him.
-Flatyos, I will kill you.
-Stop, son. That's what he wants.
We must hang on until the
nightfall.
Cerkutay! Cerkutay, where are you going?
Come on, hurry!
What happened? Where are you going,
Bala Hatun? Where?
-You'll stay with me here.
-What are you doing?
What are you doing? Leave her,
take me!
Shut up, I don't need you!
Bala is my guarantee.
She'll come with me.
-Let me go!
-Tell Osman Bey!
I have his escrows!
Come on, hurry!
You don't have a guarantee now, Targun.
Come on!
Flatyos!
Don't move, I'm aiming!
Soldiers, kill him!
Come on, warriors!
Baysungur, come!
They are running away!
Soldiers, follow me!
Are you happy? Have you taken
your revenge?
What kind of a Turk are you, Göktuğ?
Answer me, treacherous dog!
What happened, Bala? Did Osman
not come to rescue you?
Or is he in a greater trouble now?
You both will die today. You won't
see each other.
The last thing you'll see will be
my face.
How is it?
Did you like that?
Savcı Bey! Savcı Bey!
We left Cerkutay behind!
If we keep waiting, his sacrifice
will be for nothing! Come on!
If they do something to him,
I'll skin them alive!
Aygül, come on!
Cerkutay doesn't die!
We need to reach the cave, come on!
Come on!
Savcı! Don't run away!
Face me like a valiant!
Oh, thank Allah!
-Uncle? Are you all right?
-I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Gündüz Bey, they didn't leave Bala.
They also have Osman Bey's chests.
It's true, my nephew. They have the
chests but save Bala first. Come on.
-All right, uncle.
-Come on.
The Alps will take you to the tribe.
We'll go and rescue Bala Hatun.
Come on! Come down, hurry!
Hurry, I said!
Come on!
-What are you waiting for? Hurry!
-Let me go!
Come here, Bala!
Come on!
Move!
Look at you! I pity you.
I hate you.
I'll tear your ugly face apart.
And you will watch it, is that so, Göktuğ?
With pleasure.
If you can't give an heir,
a son to your husband...
...why would you live,
right, Bala?
-Hurry!
-Come on!
-What are you waiting for, hurry!
-Let me go!
My bey!
-Boran Alp!
-Göktuğ! Brother!
I knew you would do it. I knew
Osman Bey wouldn't discard you.
-Are you all right, Bala?
-I'm all right.
So, that's how you die?
Bala.
My bey.
-My bey!
-Brother!
-I missed you, my bey.
-Mashallah, Göktuğ.
You did it.
Now, you will lead the Cumans.
We'll miss each other again, my bey.
Until the victory, brother.
Until the victory.
All right, my bey.
-All right, Bala Hatun.
-May Allah bless you, Göktuğ.
It's a good plan, Osman Bey.
And it will continue.
Göktuğ...
...you should leave now.
-All right.
One of the Ankara beys, Kızılbey's son
Umur Bey's daughter.
My name is Malhun Hatun.
We are answering Osman Bey's call.
Welcome.
Bala, take care of the chests.
Don't worry.
Alps!
Take Bala Hatun and Malhun Hatun
to the tribe.
Come on, alps!
Boran, we'll go to Söğüt and
find out about that caravan issue.
All right, my bey.
Come on, we must go to Söğüt
before they do.
Let's see what the caravan owners
say.
Alps.
Untie them.
Thank God. May Allah bless you, my bey.
Thank God.
May Allah bless you, my bey.
May Allah always keep you
on our head.
-Take a breath.
-Thank you, brother.
May Allah bless you, brothers.
So, tell me now.
I'm listening to you.
They raided our caravan, my bey.
We lost all our capital, my bey.
They tortured us in Söğüt, my bey.
-Then, why didn't they kill you?
-Because of our gold, my bey.
They tortured us to make us tell
them where our gold is, my bey.
For the traders, assets aren't
the shiver of life...
...but life is the shiver of the assets.
My bey, you told us to bring
a caravan...
...and if you get hurt
in Söğüt, I have the responsibility.
Süleyman...
For that reason, we think that...
...asking for compensation
is our right, my bey.
If we gave our word.
It will be that way.
Even if we die.
-Thank you, my bey.
-May Allah bless you, my bey.
But, the devil prepared dinner...
...we should find out who is
sitting at the table first.
Then, we'll take care of that.
May Allah give you a long life, my bey.
Same for all of us.
All of us.
We played our game.
But...
Do you think he is suspicious?
If he was suspicious,
you wouldn't be talking now.
Despite everything, we should
keep our guard.
If Osman woke up...
...we must put him into sleep again.
Watch them.
Thank you.
-So, you are Umur Bey's daughter?
-Yes, Selcan Hatun. Do you know my father?
Everyone knows Umur Bey in Anatolia.
You suffered so much from the Mongols.
Ever since I remember, we are moving
from here and there.
Geyhatu is attacking us over and over.
Ever since I remember, we are moving
from here and there.
Geyhatu is attacking us over and over.
My Lord's compassion and the saints'
hope are with the ones who are oppressed.
Inshallah. May our Lord and the saints
show mercy on us.
We are breathing thanks to our Lord.
May Allah praise my grandfather
Imurin Mayesefettin.
Ahmet what's going on?
Don't reveal my place.
Ahmet!
Okay.
My Bala, my beautful daughter.
We were chatting with Malhun Hatun.
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for Ahmet, mother.
Have you seen him?
No, daughter.
Ahmet is not here.
Okay then.
It looks like we were destined to meet
in the wrong time, Malhun Hatun.
I am going to be a guest of yours
if you approve, Bala Hatun.
I hope better days are waiting for us.
Now that you are our guest,
you are welcomed.
- I won! Now you run!
- Hey, son.
Go now, I'll join you.
Was that your son?
He is so sweet, Masha Allah.
No.
He is not my own.
He is all of ours.
He is an orphan.
His parents are martyred.
May my Lord praise him.
- Amin.
I want to go to my Alps,
if you excuse me.
Of course, daughter.
My Bala.
What are you thinking?
We know who she is. but we don't know
why she is here. Selcan Mother.
Isn't it obvious, my daughter?
The aimless ones don't have a path.
They can't succeed.
- It's not our business from now on.
- Yes.
She is going to talk to our Bey
about why she has come.
Saints say "Children are father's mirror"
Apparently she is valiant like her father.
Her father Umur Bey was a very
important Bey, my daughter.
His tribe immigrated from Ankara,
from Germiyan.
Let's see now where they are going to
land.
It's all because of me. Bamsi Bey.
I shouldn't have listened to you.
What were you supposed to do then?
Don't tire yourself Bamsi Bey, sit.
He doesn't listen at all, my Bey.
He tried to pray in this situation.
Bamsi Bey.
How did we fall into this trap?
We couldn't find the betrayers
in the tribe yet.
We are going to find him finally.
We are going to bait him to
wolves.
But I need to see Governor Yorga.
Only he can save us from Nicola.
Idris Bey, excuse us.
We have a private issue with Bamsi Bey.
Of course my Bey. I am leaving.
You go on.
Bamsi Bey, if there is anything you
need. I'm right outside.
Osman Bey, Idris Bey has heard that
you are going to meet Governor Yorga.
I am about to find the betrayer,
Bamsi Bey.
- Let's see if Nicola hears about this.
- You are suspicious of Idris.
- I already suspected him.
- Me too.
We are going to find out,
My Brother Gunduz, Abdurrahman Ghazi and
alps are on their way.
We haven't heard from my brother Savci yet.
Aygul is with them also.
Apparently...
They took Vladius' bait.
Don't worry, Osman Bey.
Cerkutay and Aygul are with them.
Yes, Bamsi Bey, yes.
Let me go to my Sheik now.
I see you well, Masha Allah.
Eyvallah, eyvallah (thank you) Osman Bey.
Take my greetings to him.
As soon as I become alright, I'll visit
him too.
Eyvallah(okay) Bamsi Bey.
Eyvallah.
Hello Gonca Hatun.
Thank you.
What are these?
I am organizing the provisions
for Sogut.
Thanks to Bala Hatun, the ones who are in
need will get these.
May Allah praise her.
May Allah praise you too, Boran.
I heard that you saved Bala from those
bandits,
- If it wasn't for you...
- Thanks to our Bey, Gonca Hatun.
Gonca Hatun, what are you doing.
You are going to hurt yourself.
Do you think I'm such an easy girl?
I know you are not easy.
But if you get hurt, I get hurt.
Speed up, Boran Bey.
There are lots of things to do.
Thank you Hatuns.
Everything is ready.
You can take your rest.
- Are the tents for my Alps ready?
- Sure. They are all our guests.
Is there a problem?
Your Hatuns weave rugs. carpets.
Right?
True.
Why are you asking?
I liked the cloth in Damascus.
These are fine as well.
Our Hatuns are the best when it comes to
being dexterous.
The world is large, Bala Hatun.
You need to travel to know that.
So you and your Bey couldn't find a
place to stay.
I don't have a Bey(husband)
Why?
I am waiting for someone to show up.
The world is large, Malhan Hatun.
I am sure you'll find someone.
You keep looking.
Don't worry Bala Hatun.
My Bey is going to be a son of Bey.
I am sure he'll find this daughter of Bey
someday.
Good night.
Here you sit, my sheik.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate)
We have been looking forward to
seeing you. You honored our tribe.
- Thank you.
- Of course, my Bey.
Thank Allah that I get to see Ertugrul
Ghazi's son Osman Bey.
Amin.
We witness that you follow the path
of religion and traditions.
May you be blessed.
Amin my sheik.
Can I, father?
Of course.
Come here.
Be righteous like you are ordered to be.
Don't let them pervert you and
tell them this:
"I believed in Allah's book...
and I was ordered to bring justice
to you."
Allah says this in his book.
And Hadrat Ayse said this:
Whoever is the leader of a
community...
he should be judicious...
so that his way shall be enlightened.
and if someone doesn't care
about justice...
while he is in charge...
his way shall be dark.
May your way be clear, my Bey.
May Allah bless your generation.
- Amin.
Turk's and Islam's dagger stabbed
on Byzantine.
May my Allah let your children
to take your throne which...
My Ancestor Ertugrul Ghazi
left for you...
Amin my sheik.
Amin.
Don't shout for nothing.
It hurts.
Now it really hurts.
Why are you looking like that?
It shines like that when moonlight shines
on your sword.
Like what?
Like your eyes.
Baysungur.
Try again.
Okay my Bey.
They are still waiting, my Bey.
They are trying to leave us hungry and
dehydrated.
We need to get out of here.
- We have to take revenge for Dumrul.
- My Bey...
If they hadn't had a crossbow...
we could escape in the darkness.
True, Baysungur.
True.
What's it now?
I surrounded them like spider web.
But Osman got away again.
Your spiders are bad at netting.
I was about to kill him, Petrus...
That woman...
came out suddenly with her alps.
Like she dropped out of sky.
Which woman?
Malhun Hatun!
Malhun Hatun.
I know her name.
I don't know her...
yet.
She is Umur Bey's daughter.
Who is Umur Bey?
He is one of the strongest Beys of
Oghuz Turkmens around Ankara.
Damn vandals! They scattered into our
lands like grasshoppers.
What is Ankara Turkmen's daughter
doing here?
She is doing Whatever Ertugrul did
and whatever Osman is doing here!
Her grandfather Seyfettin Kızıl was one of
the Beys Sultan Aladdin trusted the most.
But when Aladdin died, Seyfettin's son...
rioted new Sultan Gıyasettin and Mongols.
Genghis' dogs killed him in Kirsehir
at the end.
Since then, they have had a feud
with Mongols.
They are going to form an alliance with
Osman in order to defeat Geyhatu.
So he sent his daughter.
Bravo Nicola, Bravo.
I'll tell how wise you are to Pope.
So that conquer Osman was planning
has started.
We are going to wake up with their sheep's
bell, not our Church's bell!
And Pope is not able to have the documents
he needs in order to locate Turk Boys..
Because of your stupid actions!
Tell me my sheik.
Over the seven seas, what is the...
situation of Turks and Islam?
We are like what we deserve.
Muslim attack Muslims, Turk attacks Turks.
The arrow of Muslims aim other Muslims.
The sword of Muslims rise against
other Muslims.
Damascus is miserable.
Baghdad is blasted.
Aleppo is miserable too.
And so is Anatolia.
There is no government, no regulation.
I have seen such places that people
want to die, my Bey.
They think they are Sultans, Governors.
If you can't unite, even golden throne
can't save your state, my Bey.
The lasting thing is not the throne,
but the state.
- What is going to happen?
- We'll see.
You tell me.
I'm working for my grandfather Suleiman
Shah and my father Ertugrul Ghazi's bequest
What is their bequest, son?
The blood, shedding from Erzurum highlands
to Aleppo deserts...
want a glorious state.
Sure, son. sure.
This is what the world of Islam and
Turks are waiting for.
Like a rooted tree sprouting from
its trunk...
A glorious state that all the oppressed
ones can take shelter under it.
This is what we are working on.
We invite all Turkish tribes running
away from Mongols.
This is all I am working for.
The wisest Ahis in Anatolia are
in my land.
The soldiers who want to battle madly
are in my army.
Our Hatuns with swords in their belt
are more willing to battle than their men.
They'll come.
You'll accommodate them.
You'll give them grassland.
You'll give them home.
- I'll kill Targun with my own...
- Of course.
I can resurrect her for you to
kill her twice.
We couldn't get the documents, right.
But we know what Osman wants to do.
Don't we?
Turkmen tribes are scattered all around
in Anatolia, running away from Mongols.
Osman wants to have them, inviting them
to join him.
He will give them the lands he took
from us!
So you now realize Osman will promise
your lands to...
Other Turkish tribes in order to
make them join him.
Great.
Excellent.
But the real question is that:
You, Governor Nicola, what is
your plan against Osman?
I'll do what I have to do
Ahi will produce, soldiers will fight
the infidels.
Hatuns will support.
We'll grow together.
This had always been like that
until mongols came, son.
Think of your ancestor Hadrat
Keykubat Khan.
He conquered Alaiye and Sinop.
He united Mediterranean and
Black sea.
He united everyone in his palace.
He protected oppressed ones,
all the Turkmens.
He established medical centers.
He established schools.
His courts were judicious.
Inshallah my sheik.
Our will in our hearts...
are all for our state.
Ahis, valiants, and Hatuns.
There is one more class. Of course you
can establish a state with those, too.
But it's unclear that it becomes
everlasting.
Saints are necessary.
Ahis, Ghazis, Hatuns.
And Dervishes.
You should know that dervishes
are also necessary.
Dervishes bless you.
My grandfather Gark...
My grandfather Hayrani...
Hunkar Bektas from Karacahoyuk...
they all pray for you.
And my father Taptuk prays for you too.
I appreciate their prays.
I got to see your face.
I heard that you became Bey.
I have a gift for you.
I really appreciate it.
You should take it.
Gifts are to be taken.
Your gift is a verse from Dervish Yunus.
"Our state lives long thanks to these
saints we have and will have"
Dervishes are wise, think about this.
The verses of Dervish Yunus
make you think eventually.
I hope you take the meaning out
of this verse, son.
State is dervishes' breath and dervishes
becomes breath to the state.
You warmed me.
You enlightened me my sheik.
Insha Allah the new state of Turks and
Islam becomes breath for dervishes.
Elhamdulillah ( thanks to Allah).
Ah Cerkutay Ah!
Why are you leaving without informing
anyone!?
What kind of horse is this?
Ah you mad boy!
Where is he already?
Cerkutay is coming!
Where have you been?
We got the crossbow, and of course
the owner of this.
What is this?
My Bey.
Cerkutay can't be hungry.
Okay let's eat, you need to
gather your strength.
Baysungur, go eat.
My Bey.
You are welcome.
My Allah, give me patience.
Eyvallah son.
(thank you)
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
( In the name of Allah, The Most Gracious and The Most Merciful)
Eyvallah. (thanks)
Can I come, my Hanım?
How are my Alps?
- We are settled.
- Do you need anything?
- No, my Hanım.
As I said, you keep your eyes open,
keep your mouth shut.
I want to know what happens in
here and in Sogut.
Of course, my Hanım.
It's time to talk to Osman Bey.
Come on Dundar Bey.
This is not good.
- Let's eat something.
- No Hatun.
I don't want to eat. It's not time
to eat.
I know.
Even if you cooperated with that infidel,
Osman is still sitting on his throne.
But there is no way back, Dündar Bey.
When a wolf reveals himself, he cannot
go back, he must fight.
He must.
You are right, Hatun, but...
What are we going to do with the
troubles that wolf encounters?
Potter Idris...
he knows everything.
That I cooperated with Governor Nicola,
I helped them to raid the tribe.
He knows everything.
What are you talking about my Bey?
How did he learn this?
It's not the case. From now on,
every breath the Potter takes...
tightens the rope Osman Bey whipped
on my neck.
What is your plan?
My plan is to get rid of him.
My dearie Bala...
Every people has a challenge.
Our love's challenge is this, my Bala.
We obey whatever our Allah orders.
I'll have a new Hatun.
This time for real.
Bala.
What are you brooding on?
One trouble ends, another one starts
my Osman.
My path is like your hair.
sometimes knotty, sometimes straggly.
I love it in every shape.
My Bala, my heart is in the darkness
of your hair.
So you accept your troubles.
If your eyes were troubling,
if your lips were poisonous...
I'd still accept anything that comes
from you.
Can I, Osman Bey?
Let me check this Hatun.
Come!
What's it about, Malhun Hatun.
Osman Bey I have a question for you.
- Couldn't you wait until morning?
- My father is waiting for an answer.
What's it?
Osman Bey, we came here with your
invitation.
We are here to shed blood, we are here
to die.
But we saw a raided tribe,
captured Hatuns.
- We didn't ask for your help Malhun Hatun.
- Osman Bey, this is not our issue.
We are going to settle here, our destiny
is up to you.
But we are not coming with five tents.
We have ten thousand men.
You can't even count.
It's my father Umur Bey's question,
forgive me. Don't shoot the messenger.
But, tell me Osman Bey.
Can you handle that?
It's not the right time or
place to talk about it.
Welcome.
I have things to tell Efendi Petrus.
O, the Holy heart of Jesus...
the infinite center of love...
the infinite ocean of grace...
the consolation of broken-hearted...
the shelter of sinners....
and the hope of the world.
None of us is attached to Jesus like you.
My brother Petrus.
How can we expect good things...
when we betray him like that?
Ever since I came to Osman's lands...
I haven't heard any good news.
Then you'll love what you'll hear.
Osman made an alliance
agreement with Yorgo.
I thought Nikola should know.
Then tell Nikola about this news.
David.
I had better
go back to the tent, Efendi Petrus.
You'll get a reward if you tell him.
I think it should be
you who will tell Nikola about it, David.
Then I should go now.
If we don't hear from the potter again...
we know why.
If he watches him...
he may reach us soon.
We're traders, Melik.
Everyone can come to our workplace.
His governors are leaving Nikola.
Nikola's weakness won't endanger...
our Holy father's passion for these lands.
How will we do it?
Like Osman did.
With alliance.
With Mongols, right?
If I were Geyhatu...
I wouldn't send my soldiers...
without an ally.
With whom they will ally?
Do you think Nikola will do it?
Osman is his greatest enemy.
But it doesn't mean that
he'll let Geyhatu's people in.
The governor that will replace Nikola...
may collaborate.
What if Osman finds out we're involved?
What will we do then?
We're not sure if he suspected us.
Then we'll destroy his suspicions.
How?
- They're gone, sir.
- How?!
We're here, Flatyos.
- We're coming.
- Soldiers! Kill them!
Allah is eternal!
I'll kill you.
I will kill you and your father here.
Hold on, son!
I'm here, brother.
Brother!
He's leaving!
Come on Alps!
Son!
Are you okay?
My Bamsı Bey. Is he okay?
Yes, son. Don't worry.
Thank Allah.
I couldn't kill him, father.
I couldn't kill Flatyos.
Brother.
You are here in time.
Where is Dumrul Alp?
Thank you.
I feel sorry for Aksu Sister.
Her funeral was as nice as her.
While she was trying to save me...
What's wrong with you, Bala?
You said I shouldn't come because of my
pain but you're the one with pain.
You're sorry for Aksu Bacı.
But there's something
else you're sorry for.
Thank you.
Come on.
Eat.
I'm angry with you.
You don't listen to me.
Why are you here?
May it be easy, Hatuns.
Thank you, Hatun.
What, Malhun Hatun?
Yesterday, the Kayı Tent. Today, Söğüt.
Are you here to examine?
I've heard about this soup kitchen.
I'm proud.
I wanted to see it myself.
So, you'll leave then.
Mashallah.
Muslims, non-Muslims...
I'm happy that you love it.
You said hard things to
Osman Bey yesterday.
- He said nothing but...
- He is Bey, who is the son a Bey.
I'm a daughter of a Bey.
We've talked about the
future of our tents.
And you've listened to us, obviously.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.)
My Sheik.
You'll live here from now on.
I know you want us to be comfortable.
However, this comfort may
extend our way to go.
The dervishes, the students and workers.
They may stay here, we think.
Come, please.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.)
We frequently say your name recently.
May it be good, Inshallah.
When Kayqubad came to Elbistan...
he visited Dede Garkın...
and he found him in a wreck then he felt
upset.
He gave him a mansion.
Just as Sultanu'l Ulema Bahattin...
did to him during a visit to Konya.
Who else can beg Allah like that?
Both of them...
said that staying with students in
Madrasah will be good for them.
May Allah give us the way to follow him.
Amin, my Sheik.
This place will be full of the
voices of dervishes, Inshallah.
Scribes and muftis who will
serve our holy state...
will be raised here.
If people have a problem, they
will come here.
In the presence of scribes...
soldiers and Beys will be equal.
What the justice and the tradition
say will happen.
What do you think, my Abdal?
Is the secret solved?
You know every secret, my Pir.
That's good, son.
May Allah complete your intentions.
If there's
no justice, the sky will collapse on us.
A state's religion is justice, Ali said.
- May Allah bless him.
- Amin.
Where are you going, my Bey?
It's time, Hatun.
Will you do it in the tent?
Do you think I'm novice?
I know the potter is in Söğüt.
I need to finish this.
Inshaallah.
Take care, my Bey.
Don't worry.
Making a sculpture
of a flawless face is hard.
I think it's the best work I do.
You're being unfair to yourself, Nikola.
You're a great artist and a big commander.
Yes, if we don't
count my failures against Osman.
David wants to see you, sir.
Let him in.
Your wounds heal quickly.
I think your father's prayers worked out.
My wounds heal quickly.
But what I'm
going to tell you will upset you.
Yorgo accepted to collaborate with Osman.
Isn't it such big news for a potter?
Don't believe in everything you've heard.
Osman said that himself.
I thought you should know.
Get out, David.
Yorgo! Yorgo!
I will host him here.
Let's see if he appreciates
my art as you do.
Your anger is my anger, your
revenge is my revenge.
We'll take revenge on Nikola...
who killed Targun and...
spoiled our collaboration.
We will, so that everyone will see what
it's like to play a trick on Cumans.
We'll take Nikola's goods
and then kill him.
We won't stop
until Targun's soul is in peace.
Revenge! Revenge! Revenge!
Revenge! Revenge!
We want to see our Osman Bey.
My Bey. Merchant Melik wants to see you.
Let him come.
Tell me. What's that important?
My Osman Bey...
We trusted your word and...
we brought a caravan.
We kept our words...
however...
- why do you suspect my words?
- No, my Bey!
However, as the time flies, we're at harm.
Forgive us, my Bey.
We dealt with so much.
There are so many bandits around.
However, even in Germiyans...
in Chobanids...
our waste is covered
with the courts, my Bey.
- Who made you suspect my justice?
- No, my Bey.
No...
Then what do you want?
We want a court, my Bey.
However, we know that...
you adjudge.
However...
you don't have any court or kadi.
So, you want a court.
You want a court...
you...
think my justice will appear late...
as you please, then.
The kadi of this court...
is Sheik Edebalı.
- Thank you, my Bey.
Thank you.
If you excuse us.
My Bey, the potter went to Governor
Nikola.
He's coming to Söğüt now.
May it be good.
We have martyrs!
We have martyr!
My son.
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest!)
Osman Bey. Do you have time?
We have things to talk.
Not now, Malhun Hatun.
Not now.
Alps!
You didn't say anything about
my work of art, Yorgo.
It's nice.
Nice?
Just nice?
When you look at it, do you think it's
just nice?
What else should I think?
I'll tell you what to think.
Can you see the anger of
a betrayed man, Yorgo?
Look at it.
Can you see it now?
Look.
The same face expression.
Can you see it?
Look at it.
Get this traitor out of here.
The potter.
Osman.
You hosted Yorgo nicely, Nikola.
He's unfaithful and he
doesn't know anything about art.
Traitor.
Flatyos.
Do you know anything about art?
It's from Constantinople, from
the Emperor.
What does it say?
He wants me there.
In a short time.
What does he want?
Oh, my friend...
The emperors just give orders.
They don't...
say why.
As he wants me urgent...
it means I won't have good days
in Constantinople.
My Osman Bey... Forgive me.
Spare my life, Osman Bey.
I'll kill you.
It'll be your gift.
Whose dog are you?
Who?
Who do you work for?
Tell me.
Who?
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you everything.
Those who try to betray you are the
ones who are close to you.
Who?
- Who are they?
- The one who betrays you is...
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com